<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sunfire 370 &#8211; E-commerce</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product-tag/sunfire-370/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:48:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sunfire Sonic 370</title>
		<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/</link>
					<comments>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Afaq]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/?post_type=product#038;p=31</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the fusion of boAt's excellence meets the grandeur of Asia's largest music festival, get ready for an electrifying experience! Introducing the Sunfire Sonic 370, an over-ear wireless headset that embodies the spirit of innovation and entertainment. With cutting-edge Bluetooth v5.0 technology, these headphones ensure seamless connectivity for an immersive audio experience. Get ready to immerse yourself in the rhythm and vibe of your favorite tunes with the Sunfire Sonic 370 by your side.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4><strong>Immersive Audio Experience</strong></h4>
<p>Equipped with powerful 50mm dynamic drivers, the Sunfire Sonic 370 delivers an immersive audio experience that perfectly complements your vibe, transporting you to your own musical realm.</p>
<h4><strong>Over-Ear Comfort</strong></h4>
<p>Crafted as over-ear headphones, the Sunfire Sonic 370 ensures extended comfort during your listening sessions. Its ergonomic design prioritizes your comfort, allowing you to indulge in long hours of uninterrupted music enjoyment.</p>
<h4><strong>Dynamic Sound Performance</strong></h4>
<p>Featuring moving coil drivers, these headphones produce dynamic sound quality that resonates with clarity and precision. With an impedance of 32Ω and a sensitivity of 90dB±3dB, every beat is delivered with remarkable detail.</p>
<h4><strong>Extended Playback Time</strong></h4>
<p>With a battery capacity of 500mAh, the Sunfire Sonic 370 provides an impressive playback time of up to 20 hours on a single charge. Say goodbye to frequent recharging and immerse yourself in music for extended periods.</p>
<h4><strong>Seamless Connectivity</strong></h4>
<p>Utilizing Bluetooth version V5.0, these headphones offer seamless connectivity with all Bluetooth-enabled devices. Enjoy wireless freedom with a range of up to 10 meters, allowing you to move around without being tethered to your device.</p>
<p><strong>Reliable Performance</strong></p>
<p>Designed and imported by Imagine Marketing Limited, the Sunfire Sonic 370 ensures reliable performance and durability. Its compatibility with all Bluetooth devices makes it a versatile choice for all your audio needs.</p>
<p><strong>Technical Specifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Driver Size: 50mm</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 20Hz-20KHz</li>
<li>Charging Time: 2.5 hours</li>
<li>Standby Time: 180 hours</li>
<li>Country Of Origin: China</li>
<li>Net Quantity: 1</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
