<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Headphones &#8211; E-commerce</title>
	<atom:link href="https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product-tag/headphones/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 03:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/wp-content/uploads/2024/04/cropped-cropped-image_processing20210913-21444-aulnwx-removebg-preview-e1712887160567-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Headphones &#8211; E-commerce</title>
	<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sunfire Sonic 370</title>
		<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/</link>
					<comments>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Afaq]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/?post_type=product#038;p=31</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the fusion of boAt's excellence meets the grandeur of Asia's largest music festival, get ready for an electrifying experience! Introducing the Sunfire Sonic 370, an over-ear wireless headset that embodies the spirit of innovation and entertainment. With cutting-edge Bluetooth v5.0 technology, these headphones ensure seamless connectivity for an immersive audio experience. Get ready to immerse yourself in the rhythm and vibe of your favorite tunes with the Sunfire Sonic 370 by your side.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4><strong>Immersive Audio Experience</strong></h4>
<p>Equipped with powerful 50mm dynamic drivers, the Sunfire Sonic 370 delivers an immersive audio experience that perfectly complements your vibe, transporting you to your own musical realm.</p>
<h4><strong>Over-Ear Comfort</strong></h4>
<p>Crafted as over-ear headphones, the Sunfire Sonic 370 ensures extended comfort during your listening sessions. Its ergonomic design prioritizes your comfort, allowing you to indulge in long hours of uninterrupted music enjoyment.</p>
<h4><strong>Dynamic Sound Performance</strong></h4>
<p>Featuring moving coil drivers, these headphones produce dynamic sound quality that resonates with clarity and precision. With an impedance of 32Ω and a sensitivity of 90dB±3dB, every beat is delivered with remarkable detail.</p>
<h4><strong>Extended Playback Time</strong></h4>
<p>With a battery capacity of 500mAh, the Sunfire Sonic 370 provides an impressive playback time of up to 20 hours on a single charge. Say goodbye to frequent recharging and immerse yourself in music for extended periods.</p>
<h4><strong>Seamless Connectivity</strong></h4>
<p>Utilizing Bluetooth version V5.0, these headphones offer seamless connectivity with all Bluetooth-enabled devices. Enjoy wireless freedom with a range of up to 10 meters, allowing you to move around without being tethered to your device.</p>
<p><strong>Reliable Performance</strong></p>
<p>Designed and imported by Imagine Marketing Limited, the Sunfire Sonic 370 ensures reliable performance and durability. Its compatibility with all Bluetooth devices makes it a versatile choice for all your audio needs.</p>
<p><strong>Technical Specifications:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Driver Size: 50mm</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 20Hz-20KHz</li>
<li>Charging Time: 2.5 hours</li>
<li>Standby Time: 180 hours</li>
<li>Country Of Origin: China</li>
<li>Net Quantity: 1</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-370/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hussar Magicbuds</title>
		<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/hussar-magicbuds/</link>
					<comments>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/hussar-magicbuds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Afaq]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/?post_type=product#038;p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the best of boAt meets Asia’s biggest music festival, you are bound to have a blast! Meet the over-ear wireless headset, boAtxSunburn Rockerz 558. The headphones come equipped with the latest Bluetooth v5.0 for instant wireless connectivity. Its powerful 500mAh battery provides playtime of up to 20 hours for you to groove nonstop! The 50mm dynamic drivers bring alive your favourite tunes through its thumping bass. Hear every beat as it drops with the bombastic Rockerz 558.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4><strong>Immersive Audio Experience</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>Dynamic Drivers:</strong> Equipped with powerful 50mm dynamic drivers, these headphones deliver immersive audio that perfectly complements your mood and creates your own personal zone.</li>
</ul>
<h4><strong>Designed for Comfort</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>Over-Ear Design:</strong> Enjoy supreme comfort with the over-ear design that ensures a snug fit for extended listening sessions.</li>
</ul>
<h4><strong>Impressive Technical Specifications</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>Driver Type:</strong> Utilizes moving coil drivers for exceptional sound reproduction.</li>
<li><strong>Driver Size:</strong> Large 50mm drivers for deep bass and crisp highs.</li>
<li><strong>Impedance:</strong> 32Ω impedance for compatibility with a wide range of devices.</li>
<li><strong>Sensitivity:</strong> Boasts a sensitivity of 90dB±3DB for clear and detailed sound.</li>
<li><strong>Frequency Response:</strong> Covers the full range of audible frequencies from 20Hz to 20KHz.</li>
<li><strong>Battery Capacity:</strong> Features a 500mAh battery for extended playback time.</li>
<li><strong>Playback Time:</strong> Enjoy up to 20 hours of continuous playback on a single charge.</li>
<li><strong>Charging Time:</strong> Quick 2.5-hour charging time for minimal downtime.</li>
<li><strong>Standby Time:</strong> Offers a standby time of up to 180 hours for added convenience.</li>
<li><strong>Bluetooth Connectivity:</strong> Supports Bluetooth version V5.0 for seamless wireless connectivity.</li>
<li><strong>Bluetooth Range:</strong> Provides a range of up to 10 meters for hassle-free mobility.</li>
</ul>
<h4><strong>Premium Quality</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>Country of Origin:</strong> Manufactured in China with a focus on quality craftsmanship.</li>
<li><strong>Compatibility:</strong> Compatible with all Bluetooth-enabled devices for versatile usage.</li>
<li><strong>Net Quantity:</strong> Each package contains 1 unit of the product.</li>
<li><strong>Imported and Marketed By:</strong> Imported and marketed by Imagine Marketing Limited.</li>
</ul>
<h4><strong>Ergonomic Design</strong></h4>
<ul>
<li><strong>Optimized for Comfort:</strong> Designed with ergonomics in mind, ensuring maximum comfort during long listening sessions.</li>
<li><strong>Long-lasting Enjoyment:</strong> Experience uninterrupted music enjoyment with Hussar Magicbuds, designed to prioritize your comfort and musical satisfaction.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/hussar-magicbuds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunfire Sonic 558</title>
		<link>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-558/</link>
					<comments>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-558/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Afaq]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 02:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/?post_type=product#038;p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When the fusion of boAt's excellence meets Asia’s premier music festival, get ready for an electrifying experience! Introducing the over-ear wireless headset, the Sunfire Sonic 558 by boAtxSunburn. Featuring the latest Bluetooth v5.0 technology, enjoy instant wireless connectivity like never before. Powered by a robust 500mAh battery, indulge in a whopping 20 hours of uninterrupted playtime to keep you grooving all day long! With 50mm dynamic drivers delivering immersive audio, immerse yourself in your favorite tunes with pulsating bass. Feel the pulse of every beat as the Sunfire Sonic 558 delivers an explosive audio experience.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3>Features</h3>
<ol>
<li>Immersive Audio Experience: Experience immersive audio that matches your vibe and sets your zone with the Sunfire Sonic 558&#8217;s 50mm dynamic drivers.</li>
<li>Over-Ear Comfort: Designed with over-ear comfort in mind, these headphones ensure that your long grooving sessions are enjoyable without compromising on comfort.</li>
<li>Dynamic Sound Drivers: Equipped with powerful 50mm dynamic drivers, these headphones deliver high-quality audio that matches your every beat.</li>
<li>Long-lasting Playback: With a battery capacity of 500mAh, enjoy up to 20 hours of uninterrupted playback time on a single charge.</li>
<li>Bluetooth Connectivity: Featuring Bluetooth version 5.0, these headphones offer seamless connectivity with all Bluetooth-enabled devices within a range of 10 meters.</li>
<li>Fast Charging: With a charging time of just 2.5 hours, you can quickly recharge your headphones for extended listening sessions.</li>
<li>Ergonomic Design: The Sunfire Sonic 558 is ergonomically designed to prioritize your comfort, ensuring that you can groove to your heart&#8217;s content without any discomfort.</li>
</ol>
<h3><strong>Specifications:</strong></h3>
<ul>
<li>Headphone Type: Over-Ear</li>
<li>Driver Type: Moving Coil Driver</li>
<li>Impedance: 32Ω</li>
<li>Sensitivity: 90dB±3DB</li>
<li>Frequency Response: 20Hz-20KHz</li>
<li>Standby Time: 180 hours</li>
<li>Compatibility: All Bluetooth Devices</li>
<li>Country Of Origin: China</li>
<li>Imported And Marketed By: Imagine Marketing Limited</li>
<li>Net Quantity: 1</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://afaqwaheed.github.io/ecommerce/product/sunfire-sonic-558/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
